<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Sharon Lee-->

<lixiaow>

	<title>Sharon's Book List</title>
	
	<sName sNumber="991000000" sProgram="Software Development and Network Engineering">Sharon Lee</sName>

		<book>
			<bookName bookimg="lj.jpg">Learning Java</bookName>
			<description bookType="programing">Java is the preferred language for many of 
			today’s leading-edge technologies-everything from smartphones and game consoles 
			to robots, massive enterprise systems, and supercomputers.</description>
			<authorName>Patrick Niemeyer</authorName>
			<publisherName>O'Reilly Media</publisherName>
			<price>$42.06</price>
			<personalReview>You’ll learn powerful new ways to manage resources and exceptions 
			in your applications, and quickly get up to speed on Java’s new concurrency utilities, 
			and APIs for web services and XML. You’ll also find an updated tutorial on how to get started 
			with the Eclipse IDE, and a brand-new introduction to database access in Java.</personalReview>
		</book>
		<book>
			<bookName bookimg="nutshell.jpg">Nutshell</bookName>
			<description bookType="fiction">Nutshell is an altogether original story of deceit and murder, 
			told by a narrator with a perspective and voice unlike any in recent literature.</description>
			<authorName>Ian McEwan</authorName>
			<publisherName>Knopf Canada</publisherName>
			<price>$17.79</price>
			<personalReview>Love and betrayal, life and death come together in the most unexpected, 
			moving ways in this sensational new novel from Ian McEwan, which will make readers first gasp 
			with astonishment then laugh with delight. Dazzling, funny and audacious, 
			it is the finest recent work from a true master, beautifully told, brilliantly executed.</personalReview>
		</book>
		<book>
			<bookName bookimg="inferno.jpg">Inferno</bookName>
			<description bookType="fiction">The darkest places in hell are reserved for those 
			who maintain their neutrality in times of moral crisis.</description>			
			<authorName>Dan brown</authorName>
			<publisherName>Doubleday</publisherName>
			<price>$7.40</price>
			<personalReview>Inferno is a sumptuously entertaining read—a novel that will captivate readers 
			with the beauty of classical Italian art, history, and literature . . . while also posing 
			provocative questions about the role of cutting-edge science in our future.</personalReview>
		</book>
		<book>
			<bookName bookimg="lop.jpg">Life of Pi</bookName>
			<description bookType="fiction">One boy. One boat. One tiger. "Life is a story... 
			You can choose your story... A story with God is the better story."</description>
			<authorName>Yann Martel</authorName>
			<publisherName>Mariner Books</publisherName>
			<price>$8.92</price>
			<personalReview>After the tragic sinking of a cargo ship, a solitary lifeboat remains bobbing 
			on the wild, blue Pacific. The only survivors from the wreck are a sixteen-year-old boy named Pi,
			a hyena, a zebra (with a broken leg), a female orangutan--and a 450-pound Royal Bengal tiger. 
			The scene is set for one of the most extraordinary and beloved works of fiction in recent years.</personalReview>
		</book>
</lixiaow>
